{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": " Maria ______ go shopping tomorrow.",
            "a": "   might",
            "b": "   may",
            "c": "   neither may nor might",
            "d": "   both may and might",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "8",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " Judy _____ that book next week.",
            "a": "   might reads",
            "b": "   may reads",
            "c": "   may read",
            "d": "   mights read",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "8",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " Bill _______ ESL next year.",
            "a": "   may teaches",
            "b": "   mays teach",
            "c": "   might teaches",
            "d": "   might teach",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "8",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " Carol may _______ a movie tonight.",
            "a": "   seen",
            "b": "   saw",
            "c": "   sees",
            "d": "   see",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "8",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " Kay might _______ Lori later.",
            "a": "   called",
            "b": "   will call",
            "c": "   call",
            "d": "   calls",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "8",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " The test ________ difficult.",
            "a": "   may being",
            "b": "   could be ",
            "c": "   might been",
            "d": "   could will be",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "8",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " Bring your umbrell It _________ rain later.",
            "a": "   could",
            "b": "   may",
            "c": "   might",
            "d": "   could or may or might",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "8",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "_____I come in, Mr. Smith?",
            "a": "Must have ",
            "b": "Shan't",
            "c": "Ought ",
            "d": "May",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "8",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "There's plenty of time. You _______ come so early.",
            "a": "needn't ",
            "b": "weren't",
            "c": "can't ",
            "d": "couldn't",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "8",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ________ have more money if you didn't spend so much.",
            "a": "may ",
            "b": "should",
            "c": "might ",
            "d": "ought",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "8",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}